http://www.ontheclock.com/privacy-policy.aspx

OnTheClock.com privacy policy
How we protect your privacy
Overview
At OnTheClock.com we recognize that privacy is important to you. This document outlines the types of personal and company information we receive and collect when you use our web based time clock, as well as some of the steps we take to protect your information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your information with us.
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Ontheclock.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us during registration, via email or other direct contact from you. We do not sell, rent, or lease your private information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, to provide support services or credit card processing.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new features, site upgrades, price changes, support services or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
1. See what data we have about you, if any.
2. Change/correct any data we have about you.
3. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Registration
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.
Sharing
We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.
We partner with another party to provide support services. When the user signs up for Ontheclock.com services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide support services for OnTheClock.com. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing support for Ontheclock.com services.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data) that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We restrict access to personal information to OnTheClock.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.
When you visit OnTheClock.com, we send one or more cookies (small files containing a string of numbers & characters) to your computer that uniquely identifies your web browser. We use cookies to improve the security and quality of our service by storing a unique number which identifies your browser to our servers.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however you can reset your browser to refuse cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, your experience using our online punch clock may be compromised if your cookies are disabled.
Consumer Recourse
If you believe we have not complied with our stated privacy policy concerning our usage of personally identifiable information that we may collect over the Internet, or that information we have provided to you based upon your Internet activity is inaccurate, you may Contact Us.
To Sum It Up
Our primary goal is to give our customers the best web clock system. We are not interested in collecting or selling your information, only in providing the best online time clock system in the world.
